evolvingwisdom.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Evolving Wisdom

## Evolving Wisdom Privacy Policy

**Who do we contact?**

Evolving Wisdom, LLC only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products.

**What information do we collect? Evolving Wisdom collects information in two categories:**

  1. **Personally Identifiable Information (PII)** Name and e-mail address – provided by you for registration to receive our free newsletters or to download recordings of our calls. Name, postal address, phone and credit card information – provided by you when purchasing our products. All such information is strictly protected and used only for delivering the content and products the user has signed up for or purchased, or for finding other men and women who may find our information valuable. This information is NEVER used for other purposes and is NEVER shared with 3rd parties for their own use.
  2. **Anonymous Usage History** This information is strictly limited to the history of activities that the user engaged in while on our site. It does NOT include any personally identifiable information.

There is a small subset of this history that we use with 3rd parties, such as Google, for the purpose of measuring and improving the efficacy of advertising campaigns.

Some of these third parties, aggregate such information across many websites. This allows them to identify users who are more likely to be interested in specific offerings like fashion, sports, education and so on.

As an Internet user, you may experience the results of such aggregation by noticing how the ads displayed on Yahoo, for example, better match your interests (the optimistic scenario), or at least more closely match a website that you recently visited.

**What are cookies/clear GIFs and how do we use them?**

**Cookies:**  Like many other commercial sites, our site utilizes standard technologies called “cookies” and clear GIFs to collect information about how our Site is used. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies were designed to help a website recognize a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the Personally Identifiable information.

**Clear GIFs:**  At times, we work with third-party service partners that employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit to help us measure advertising effectiveness. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs are not tied to your Personally Identifiable Information and only track the visitor traffic and behavior to and on our Site.

Clear GIFs can “work with” existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company’s clear GIF, the website would match the clear GIFs identifier and the advertising company’s cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the advertising company. We do, at times, provide such information to our third-party advertising service partners, but that information never includes personally identifiable information.

**How do we store your email information?**

Your email information is stored at the list server that delivers Evolving Wisdom and it’s individual program newsletters. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive these newsletters.

All of the newsletters that are sent to you by Evolving Wisdom include an unsubscribe link in them. If you have purchased any of our programs, you will continue to receive mailings related to your purchase. If you are an affiliate partner, then you will continue to receive mailings related to our affiliate program. If you would like to be removed from any of these mailings, please contact our support team here and they can assist you.

Evolving Wisdom takes all necessary industry standard precautions to maintain the security of any information you provide to us.

**Disclaimer**

This policy may be changed at any time at Evolving Wisdom’s discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website. This policy was revised February 28, 2014.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please contact us [here](https://evolvingwisdom.com/contact/). You may also send a letter to:

Evolving Wisdom, LLC  
Attn: Evolving Wisdom Support Team  
369-B 3rd St. Suite 302  
San Rafael, CA 94901
